A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976-1985.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files, 1974-1985 (Accession 37778)., Extent: x cubic feet (x boxes)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Public Safety, Secretary of, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Purchase and Supply, Div. of, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Revenue collections, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Revenue Resources and Economic Commission, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Revenue Sharing, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Reversions, 1978. (Box 41)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Senate Finance Committee, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Southeastern Association of Tax Administrators (SEATA) Conference, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Southeastern Association of Tax Administrators (SEATA) Conference, 1979. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Southeastern Association of Tax Administrators (SEATA) Executive Committee, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Southern Growth Policies Board, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Southern Legislative Conference, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Southern Legslative Conference Council of State Governments, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Speeches, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Aid to Localities, Commission on, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Corporation Commission, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Fair of Virginia, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Governmental Management, Commission on, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Governments, Council on, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Incentive Grant Program, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Owned Facilities - Public use of, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Tax Reform, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: State Tax Review, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Statutory Grants of Authority to Stage Agencies (SJR 58), 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Supplementary Fiscal Assistance Act, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Supreme Court, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Tax Administration News, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Tax limitations, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Taxation, Dept. of, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Taxation, Dept. of - Land use, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Temporary loans, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Title XX - Appropriations Committee, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Tobacco taxes, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Transportation, Secretary of, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Treasurer, State, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: University of Virginia, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Urban Assistance Incentive Fund, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Business Reports, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Council of Churches, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Stock Portfolio, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Audit Committee, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Bank of New York, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Board of Trustees, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Boston Company, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Investment Committee, 1978. (Box 42)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Massachusetts Financial, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Massachusetts Investors Trust, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Meidinger and Associates, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Peat, Marwick and Mitchell, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System (VSRS) - Putnam Advisory Companies, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: War Veterans Claims, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Washington Liaison Office, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy: Zero Base Budgeting - Sunset Legislation, 1978. (Box 43)
  - Administration and Finance - Agency Head meetings, 1978-1979. (Box 44)
  - Administration and Finance - Agency Head meeting, 1978 Aug. (Box 44)
  - Administration and Finance - Agency Head meeting, 1979 July. (Box 44)
  - Administration and Finance - Agency Head meeting, 1979 Dec. (Box 44)
  - Administration and Finance - Breakfast meetings, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Alcohol Safety Action Program, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Attorney General, Office of the, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Aviation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Bauder, Robert, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Briefing of new General Assembly members, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget), 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Alternatives and Analysis, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Budget bill, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Guidance Package Summaries, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Office and Management and Budget, U.S., 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Policy Guidance meetings, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Poliy Guidance memos, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Secretary needs, goals and policies, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Statistical information, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Targeting, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Training, 1979. (Box 44)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Secretary of Education, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Secretary of Human Resources, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Secretary of Public Safety, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Budget (Dept. of Planning and Budget) - Secretary of Transporation, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretaries, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretary of Education, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretary of Education, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretary of Human Resources, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretary of Public Safety, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Memos to Secretary of Transportation, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Administration and Finance Goals and Objectives (FY 1980), 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Cabinet meeting agenda, 1979 Mar. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Cabinet meetings, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Cabinet - Pending Cabinet meetings, 1979. (Box 45)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Accounting Project Survey Questionnairs, State Government, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Accounts, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Administration and Finance, Secretary of (Charles B. Walker), 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Administration and Finance - Agency meetings, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Administration and Finance - Agency requests for positions, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Administration and Finance - Executive Committee meetings, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Appropriations Act, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Bonds - General, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Budget Summary (1978-1980 Biennium), 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Capital Outlay Budget Tour, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: CARS, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Chase Econometric Associates / Chase forecasts, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Civil Rights Division (Washington Office of Revenue Sharing), 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Commerce and Resorces, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Commission on Local Governments, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Commissioners of Revenue, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Community Colleges, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Congressional members, U.S., 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Connock, Stuart, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Consolidated Laboratory Services, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Consolidated Salary Authorization for Teaching and Research Staff, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Coopers and Lybrand, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Council of State Governments, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Council of State Governments - State Government News, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Council of State Planning Agencies, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Credit Union, State Employees, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Crime Victims Compensation Program, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Criminal Justice, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Digest of Acts of the General Assembly, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Education, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Education, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Education, Secretary of - Issues Analysis 70/30 Plan, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Elections, State Board of, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Employment Commission, Virginia, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Fairfax Amendments, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Federal Executive Institute, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Federal Tax - Exclusions of payments, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Federation of Tax Administrators, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Fiscal impact statements, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: General Account Balance and Investment Yield, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: General Assembly members - Correspondence, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: General Fund Revenues, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: General Services, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Goochland Campus Study (J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College), 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor Dalton, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Office - Cabinet meetings, 1979. (Box 47)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Radford College, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Revenue assumptions, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Renovations / Furnishings for Federal Reserve Bank, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Renovations for Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Reynolds, J. Sargeant Community College, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Rowland, William B., 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Science Museum of Virginia, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Service charges, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Sorrell, Ray, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Special assignments ot Dept. of Planning and Budget staff, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: State Police, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Supreme Court, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Tangier Island, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Taxation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Telecommunications Council, Virginia Public (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Training Sessions for Program Budgeting, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Transportation, Secretary of, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: University of Virginia, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Commonwealth University, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Military Institute, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Extension Division Task Force, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Port Authority, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - 14th Street Tower financing, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Water Control Board, State, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Welfare, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: William and Mary, College of, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System - State office buildings financed through, 1979. (Box 46)
  - Capital Outlay Budget Tour, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Capital Outlay recommendations, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Central Accounting, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Chrysler Corporation - Loan Guarantee, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Civil disturbances - Emergency response procedure, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Commonwealth Attorneys, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Community Colleges, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Community Colleges, Dept. of - Special training, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Community Colleges, Dept. of - Survey, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), 1979. (Box 48)
  - Comptroller, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Comptroller - Accounting system, 1979. (Box 48)
  - Consolidated Laboratory Services, Div. of, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Consultants, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Corrections, Dept. of - Mental health, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Council of Criminal Justice, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Crime Commission, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Delinquency accounts, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Education Aid Authorities - Consolidation, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Education, State Board of, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, Office of, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Energy Assistance Program for the Needy, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Energy conservation, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Energy Plan, State, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Energy, U.S. Dept. of, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Environmental impact statements, 1979. (Box 49)
  - Fair Taxes for Virginians, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Federal Coordination Process, 1978. (Box 50)
  - Fire Marshall, State, 1978. (Box 50)
  - Forms Management Program, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Architectural and Engineering firms, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Biennial review of state owned land, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Confederate memorial care, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of - Leases, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Engineering and Buildings, Div. of - Office space, 1979. (Box 50)
  - General Services, Dept. of - Surplus property / Land Management, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Governor Dalton, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Governor's Office - Manson, Jennifer Joy, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Governor's Office - Miscellaneous, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Governor's Office - Murray, Larry, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Governor's Office - Speeches, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Health, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Higher Education, Institute of, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Higher Education, State Council of, 1979. (Box 50)
  - Healthcare Reports - Mental Health Institutions and Correctional Facilities, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Highways and Transportation, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Housing and Community Development, Office of, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Housing Development Authority, Virginia, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Intergovernment Affairs, Dept. of - Federal Regional Council, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of - Social Security payments, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of - Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Interstate Cooperation, Commission on, 1979. (Box 51)
  - James Madison University, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1978-1979. (Box 51)
  - Korean-Vietnam War History Commission, 1979. (Box 51)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor Dalton - Correspondence answered by the Office of Administration and Finance, 1979. (Box 52)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy / Director, Dept. of Planning and Budget: Governor's Office - Cabinet meetings, 1979. (Box 52)